SWAGAT RAORANE

PROJECT MANAGER (TL) | LOGICSERVE DIGITAL

Mumbai | raorane.swagat@gmail.com | +91 97699 19449

PROFILE

I am seasoned web developer with nearly 9 years of experience in Microsoft Technology. Currently, I am heading the development wing of LogicServe Digital as the Project Manager, having worked on the organisation's Coupon, Compare, and Digital domains. Recently, I was assigned the task to design database for a Cloud based product which my current company is in process of launching shortly. I have designed the core database along with various user screens for this product.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Company: LogicServe Digital **From Feb, 2011 to Present**

Domain: Digital Marketing

Client: Broadplace

I am working as a Project Manager, handling various projects of our UK client Broadplace. Broadplace is one of the biggest Digital Marketing agencies in the UK. I am associated with this company for more than 8 years. Initially started working offshore as Sr. **Developer and later was** promoted to Project Manager and posted onsite. Following were my responsibilities towards this client:

Platform: MVc, MVc Web API, MS SQL, Angular JS, JQuery, Google

API, Facebook API, AWS

Tools: VS 2017, MS SQL 2017

Location: Onsite (Aug 2018 to Sep 2018)

Offshore (Feb 2011 – July 2018; Sep 2018- till date)

Position: Project Manager

- Analyse: Understanding the business requirement, analysing the existing modules and its functionality. Also suggesting any changes if found necessary to enhance the functionality that will achieve utmost user's satisfaction while taking care of system performance and available resources.
- Documenting: Documenting the requirement (General understanding and Technical document)
- Estimation: Estimating the development.
- Approval: Get the technical and effort estimation approved from the concerned person.
- Development: Developing new modules and/or modifying the existing modules along with the team, to incorporate user requirement into the existing system.

- Code Review: Review code and logics written by other team members, assuring the coding standard to be as desired by Broadplace.
- Testing: Testing the new / modified functionality, assuring proper incorporation of user's requirement.
- Timely Delivery: As a Project Manager it was my core duty to make sure the timely completion and submission of the project.

Following are few important projects successfully developed and deployed for Broadplace on Angular JS and MVC:

- CampaignHero App (in progress) [Web API, Ionic, MS SQL, Google API, Facebook API]: CampaignHero App is completely different approach to manage users' google AdWords, Facebook Ads, Bing Ads Account. All from your phone, no contracts, plain English Assistance in delivering results for your business that suits the way you work. Easier way to keep track of all your digital marketing campaign.
- CampaignHub [Angular js, MVC, MS SQL]: Campaignhub helps account manager to manage a clients AdWords, Facebook, Bing Account. It helps in managing Portfolio of Account Managers, Clients, and Projects. It gives Real runtime - Dashboard with Clients SEM campaign of AdWords / Facebook and Bing Ads, Account Performance & Budget detail information. Automated reports mailed to the clients daily- Account performance/ Keyword level & Ad Group level.
- macafeeoffers.com [Asp.net, MS SQL]: This is an e-Commerce Website build to sell McAfee Licenses for UK clients.

Company: LogicServe Digital **From Feb, 2011 to Present**

Domain: Digital Marketing

Client: In-House

Following are few important projects successfully developed and deployed for LogicServe Digital:

Platform: ASP.net, MVc, MVc Web API, MS SQL, Angular JS, JQuery,

Google API, Facebook API, AWS

Tools: VS 2017, MS SQL 2017

Location: Onsite (Aug 2018 to Sep 2018)

Offshore (Feb 2011 – July 2018; Sep 2018- till date)

Position: Project Manager

- MyLogidesk (in progress) [Angular JS, MVC, MS SQL, AWS]:
 MyLogidesk is completely different approach to manage
 users google AdWords, Facebook Ads, Bing Ads account.
 All from your phone, no contracts, plain English assistance
 in delivering results for your business that suits the way
 you work. Easier way to keep track of all your digital
 marketing campaign.
- CompareRaja [ASP.net, MS SQL, JQuery, JavaScript, AWS]:
 CompareRaja is the largest technology and gadget
 research site in India. We help our users research and
 decide for mobiles, laptops, computers, electronics, TV,
 audio, home appliances etc. by giving them product
 information like news, reviews, best lists, price etc
- CouponRaja [ASP.net, MS SQL, jQuery, JavaScript]:
 CouponRaja, we curate the Best Deals and Coupon Codes from all top retailers in India and the UK and present them to our users. Our users can enjoy savings through these Coupons and also earn Extra Cashback on all their purchases!
- CouponRaja Firefox and Chrome Extension [JavaScript, jQuery]: The CompareRaja add-on is a price saving tool that saves you money while you shop online. The add-on jointly developed by CompareRaja.com & CouponRaja.com, covers 10+ key verticals including Cameras, Laptops, Books, Watches, Perfumes, Mobiles etc. and 100+ top brands. When you are looking for a product on a website, it automatically fetches the prices from multiple sites for the same product, so you can easily compare the price without having to visit multiple sites. It doesn't end here! The browser based add-on not only gets you the best price for the product but also the available coupon codes that adds to your savings. Now that's a true ADD-ON!

I am also responsible for projects developed on different platforms like PHP and WordPress, Big Query. I have successfully deployed Many PHP & WordPress Project while one is still under development and is scheduled to be completed by November end. Following are my responsibilities while working on platform other than .net.

- Analyse: Understanding the business requirement, analysing the existing modules and its functionality. Also suggesting any changes if found necessary to enhance the functionality that will achieve utmost user's satisfaction while taking care of system performance and available resources.
- Documenting: Documenting the requirement (General Understanding)
- Technical documents: Coordinate with offshore technical experts, explaining the client's requirement to them and get the technical documents and Estimation from them.
- Approvals: Get the technical document and effort estimation approved from the concerned person.
- Testing: Testing the new / modified functionality, assuring proper incorporation of user's requirement.
- Timely Delivery: As a team leader it was my core duty to make sure the timely completion and submission of the project

Following are few important projects successfully developed and deployed for Day and Ross Inc on DOT NET & MSSQL.

- Broadplace.com: This is main domain website for broadplace. We have designed and developed this website on WordPress and PHP.
- Eurovigil.in: Eurovigil Security Systems, considered as India's most advanced electronic security system, is a part of the Eureka Forbes family. Eurovigil offers highly advanced and complete security systems, which include Video Door Phones, Intrusion Alarm Systems, Home Automation Systems, CCTV Surveillance, Access Control Systems and CMS (Central Monitoring Station). All Eurovigil products carry UL, CE, FCC and ROHS certifications.
- BigQuery Report: We have set up Big Query account for SBI Life. We are generating custom report for SBI using DCM and DBM data.

Company: Annet Technologies

From July 2009 to Oct 2010

Domain: Banking

Client: Deutsche Bank

Platform: Asp.Net C# 3.5, SQL 2008

Tools: VS 2017, MS SQL 2017

Location: Onsite

Position: Software Engineer

Deutsche Bank is a leading global investment bank with a strong and profitable private clients franchise. Its businesses are mutually reinforcing. It proposed to create a multilingual website catering English and Arabic language. This website was to be built specifically for Riyadh catering Mortgage services.

Educational Qualification

QUALIFICATION

B.E. (Computers) Mumbai University in Mumbai 2004 - 2008

Diploma in .net from NIIT

Programming Languages & Technologies

Languages: C#, JavaScript, ASP.Net, WCF,MVC, MVC Web API, MS SQL, Angular JS, jQuery, Chrome & Firefox Addon,Google API,

Facebook API, AWS

Database Tools: MS SQL 2012

Web Technology: HTML

EDI TOOL: VS 2017

PERSONAL

Date of Birth:

16-Nov-1986

Address:

B/402, Laxman Tirth Apt, Near Tisai mandir, Jarimari Road, Tisgaon, Kalyan E, 421306 Thane, Maharashtra.

I hereby declare the details furnished below are true and correct, to my knowledge. In case you require documentations and recommendation, I can furnish them as and when you require.

Thank You for taking time and going through my resume,

(Signed: Swagat Raorane)

Mumbai, Date: